cirkledin.com 2019-03-11

# Privacy Policy

At Cirkled In, your privacy is very high on our priority. Please review the below privacy policy and reach out to us at [help@cirkledin.com](mailto:help@cirkledin.com) with any questions.

This privacy policy governs your use of the software application Cirkled In (Application) on any platform: website, mobile, tablet or any other device or applications. Cirkled In provides a digital platform for you to capture information that you upload about your or your kids' life achievements while connecting and collaborating with like-minded people.

### What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?

#### User Provided Information:

The Application obtains the information you provide when you download, register or use the Application. This includes an email address, your name as well as the name of your children for whom profiles are being created. In addition, all the data that you enter in a profile is obtained by the application.

#### Automatically Collected Information:

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, relating to your devices, including your device model, operating system, browser type, unique device identifier, IP address, device internet browser, mobile phone number, mobile network carrier, location and information about the way you use the Application. We will also use cookies and web beacons (pixel tags, and/or other similar technologies) to collect visitor information.

### Does the Application collect precise real-time location information of the device?

At this time, this Application does not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device.

### Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?

Only aggregated, anonymized data may be periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Application and our service. The use of this application may also include tools that let you connect with third-party services, enabling you to share your information these third-party services. By using these tools/linkages, we may transfer user submissions and information to these third-party services. In addition, these third-party services can access information on Cirkled In related to you. The use of this third-party content, websites, and services is governed by that party's own terms of service or privacy policies. We encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of third party websites and services. The Application makes no representations of the legality or rights of the content of these third-party services or use of your User Submission or information by the third party service.

We may also work with third party service providers to monitor Application for purposes such as reporting traffic and other advertising statistics. Where authorized by us, these third party providers may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our visitors. This information is collected directly by the third party. Information collected by third parties in this manner is subject to that third party's own data collection, use, and disclosure policies.

#### We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

  * Any information that you voluntarily choose to include in a publicly accessible area of the Application, such as a public profile page, will be available to anyone who has access to that content, including other users.
  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement. If Cirkled In is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.

### What are my opt-out rights?

You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by deleting your profile and account from the application.

### Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We may retain Automatically Collected information in perpetuity and may store it in aggregate.

### Children and Minimum Age Requirements

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the "Minimum Age" (defined below). To use the Application, (1) you must be the "Minimum Age" (defined below) or older and your registration and your use of the Application is in compliance with any and all applicable laws and regulations.

If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [help@cirkledin.com](mailto:help@Cirkledin.com). We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

"Minimum Age" means (a) 18 years old for the People's Republic of China, (b) 16 years old for the Netherlands, (c) 14 years old for Canada, Germany, Spain, Australia and South Korea, and (d) 13 years old for all other countries including United States. However, if the law requires that you must be older in order for Cirkled In to lawfully provide the Services to you (including the collection, storage and use of your information) then the Minimum Age is such older age. The Application is not for use by anyone under the age of 13.

### Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We take privacy and security seriously and have enabled HTTPS access to our site. We provide physical, technical, and procedural safeguards to protect the information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

### Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new [Privacy Policy](http://www.cirkledin.com/privacy_policy.php). You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. You can check the most recent version of this policy by visiting [Privacy Policy](http://www.cirkledin.com/privacy_policy.php)

### Your Consent

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us as needed. The processing means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the WA. If you reside outside the WA your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under WA privacy standards.

### Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at [help@cirkledin.com](mailto:help@cirkledin.com).
